interiorcomplex.com 2014-12-13

# Interior Complex | Privacy

Interior Complex recognizes that your privacy and the protection of your personal information is important to you and is committed to protecting your privacy. The privacy policy described below applies to the site and services offered by Interior Complex. 

BY USING THIS SITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS POLICY.

This policy was last modified in March 2013.

Interior Complex provides you with original blog posts about a variety of design topics.

What information is collected by Interior Complex:

You may use Interior Complex’s services anonymously and we will not collect any personal information about you.

What information is collected by Interior Complex via technology:

Interior Complex notes and saves information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, IP address, and IP location with each query.

Interior Complex uses cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of this or other websites you visit.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

In particular, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DoubleClick DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on your visits to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Privacy of Minors:

The Interior Complex services are not intended to be used by minors under the age of 13 and Interior Complex does not intentionally collect or maintain information from those visitors and users of the services who are under the age of 13.

When your information may be disclosed:

Interior Complex may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the requirements of the law or comply with legal process served on Interior Complex or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Interior Complex; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect personal safety of users of Interior Complex, its websites, or the public.

Updates to this privacy policy:

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the ‘last updated’ date at the top of the Privacy Policy. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

Sale of assets:

In the unlikely event that Interior Complex or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

Terms of use:

Please also visit our Terms of Use section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

Third party links:

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).

Questions and feedback:

Interior Complex welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you believe that Interior Complex has not adhered to this Policy, please contact us by using our online feedback form and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
